A Guide to the Commission on Critical Choices for Americans (CCCA) records FA484
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commission on Critical Choices for Americans (CCCA) records
Bulk, 1973-1975 1969-1978
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commission on Critical Choices for Americans
FA484
25.84 Cubic Feet 56 document boxes, 1 record storage box.
56 document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as follows:
Series 1: CCCA Meetings. Subseries 1.1: Transcripts. Subseries 1.2: Background materials. Subseries 1.3: Laurance S. Rockefeller's CCCA materials.
Series 2: Administrative. Subseries 2.1: Contracts. Subseries 2.2: Corporate Matters. Subseries 2.3: Fundraising. Subseries 2.4: Publication records.
Series 3: Financial and Personnel records. Subseries 3.1: Financial records. Subseries 3.2: Personnel records.
Series 4: Correspondence.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes general files, panel transcripts, meeting records, background papers, fundraising and contribution files, personnel files, contracts, audio tapes and financial records.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Upon its dissolution, the Third Century Corporation transferred all its net assets, including this archival collection, to the Rockefeller Archive Center.
The initial shipment of 30 storage boxes (36 cubic feet) was received by the Rockefeller Family archives in 1977 (recorded by the Family archives as accession 1977:009). Rockefeller Archive Center documentation indicates transfer of the collection in several accessions including accession 1983:025 (3.6 cu. ft.); 1983:058 and 1985:004.
Biographical / Historical
In November 1973, Nelson A. Rockefeller worked with former Delaware Governor Russell W. Peterson to establish the Commission on Critical Choices for Americans, and served as its chairman until December 1974. In December 1973, Rockefeller resigned as Governor of New York, in part to devote his efforts towards the Commission.
The Commission was a private study project on national and international policy similar to that of the Special Studies Project, directed by Henry Kissinger, and funded by the Rockefeller Brothers Fund while Nelson Rockefeller was President of the Fund from 1956-1960.
The Commission on Critical Choices for Americans was made up of a nationally representative, bipartisan group of 42 prominent Americans drawn from far-ranging fields of interest who served on a voluntary basis. Members included the majority and minority leaders of both houses of Congress.
The Commission gathered information to investigate and understand many of the challenges facing America, and published monographs, essays, studies, and research papers which identified the “critical choices” to be made and recommended possible solutions.
In August 1974, nine months after establishing the Commission, Nelson A. Rockefeller was nominated to serve as Vice President of the United States, and he was officially inaugurated as such on December 19, 1974.
Rockefeller’s lack of direct involvement had a profound impact on the work and effectiveness of the Commission. Each of the panels had planned to refine and expand the background studies, but instead the Commission chose to publish the background studies themselves.
- Commission on Critical Choices for Americans (CCCA) Meetings, 1
  - Transcripts, 1.1
    - General Commission Meeting (pg 106-311), 1973 December 3 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - General Commission Meeting, 1973 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - General Commission Meeting (pg 1-140), 1974 April 1-2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - General Commission Meeting (pg 141-270), 1974 April 1-2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - General Commission Meeting, Morning Session, 1974 April 2-3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - General Commission Meeting, 1975 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - General Commission Meeting, 1975 June 20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Panel I, Energy Meeting, 1974 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Panel I, Energy, Ecology, Economics and World Stability (pg 1-130), 1974 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Panel I, Energy, Ecology, Economics and World Stability (pg 131-260), 1974 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Panel I, Energy, Ecology, Economics and World Stability, 1974 July 19 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Panel I, Energy, Ecology, Economics and World Stability (pg 1-200), 1974 September 9 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Panel I, Energy, Ecology, Economics and World Stability (pg 201-343), 1974 September 9 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Panel I, Energy, Ecology, Economics and World Stability (pg 1-150), 1974 December 14 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Panel I, Energy, Ecology, Economics and World Stability (pg 151-308), 1974 December 14 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Panel I, Energy and Its Relationship to Ecology, Economics and World Stability, 1975 November 21 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Panel II, 1974 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Panel II, World Population, Food and Health (pg 1-100A), 1974 July 22 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Panel II, World Population, Food and Health (101-243-A), 1974 July 22 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Panel II, Food, Health, World Population and Quality of Life (1-100), 1974 September 11 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Panel II, Food, Health, World Population and Quality of Life (101-250), 1974 September 11 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Panel II, Food, Health, World Population and Quality of Life, 1975 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Panel III, Morning Session, 1974 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Panel III, Afternoon Session, 1974 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Panel III, Raw Materials, Industrial Development, Capital Formation, Employment and World Trade, 1974 July 29 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Panel III, Raw Materials, Industrial Develo pment, Capital Formation, Employment and World Trade, 1974 September 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Panel III, Raw Materials, Industrial Development, Capital Formation, Employment and World Trade, 1975 November 21 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Panel IV, Open Societies and Governments in a World of Centrally-Managed Economies (pg. 1-170), 1974 June 17 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Panel IV, Open Societies and Governments in a World of Centrally-Managed Economies (pg. 171-328), 1974 June 17 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Panel IV, Open Societies and Governments in a World of Centrally-Managed Economies (pg. 1-100), 1974 August 19 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Panel IV, Open Societies and Governments in a World of Centrally-Managed Economies (pg. 101-264), 1974 August 19 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Panel IV, Open Societies and Governments in a World of Centrally-Managed Economies (pg. 1-100), 1974 October 21 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Panel IV, Open Societies and Governments in a World of Centrally-Managed Economies (pg. 101-209), 1974 October 21 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Panel V, Meeting on World Peace, Morning Session, 1974 May 28 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Panel V, Meeting on World Peace, Afternoon Session, 1974 May 28 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Panel V, Elements Essential to World Stability and Peace (pg 1-150), 1974 August 5 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Panel V, Elements Essential to World Stability and Peace (pg 151- 239), 1974 August 4 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Panel V, Change, National Security and Peace (pg 1-130), 1974 October 9 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Panel V, Change, National Security and Peace (pg 131- 268), 1974 October 9 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Panel V, USSR and Eastern Europe Study Meeting (pg 1-150), 1974 December 13 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Panel V, USSR and Eastern Europe Study Meeting (pg 151- 302), 1974 December 13 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Panel V, USSR and Eastern Europe Study Meeting, 1974 December 14 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Panel V, Asia Study Meeting (pg 1-150), 1975 February 7 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Panel V, Asia Study Meeting (pg 151-307), 1975 February 7 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Panel V, Asia Study Meeting (pg 1-150), 1975 February 8 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Panel V, Asia Study Meeting (pg 151- 274), 1975 February 8 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Panel V, Western Europe Study Meeting (pg 1-150), 1975 February 28 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Panel V, Western Europe Study Meeting (pg 151-308), 1975 February 28 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Panel V, Western Europe Study Meeting (pg 1-150), 1975 March 1 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Panel V, Western Europe Study Meeting (pg 151-310), 1975 March 1 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Panel V, Asia Study Meeting (pg 1- 150), 1975 June 12 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Panel V, Asia Study Meeting (pg 151- 313), 1975 June 12 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Panel V, Asia Study Meeting, 1975 June 13 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Panel V, Military Aspects of Change, National Security and Peace (pg 1-150), 1975 June 19 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Panel V, Military Aspects of Change, National Security and Peace (pg 151-352), 1975 June 19 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Panel V, Change, National Security and Peace, 1975 June 20 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Panel VI, 1974 June 3 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Panel VI, Quality of Life of lndividuals and Communities (pg 1-150), 1974 August 12 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Panel VI, Quality of Life of lndividuals and Communities (pg 151-295), 1974 August 12 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Panel VI, Quality of Life of lndividuals and Communities in the USA (pg 1-140), 1974 October 29 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Panel VI, Quality of Life of lndividuals and Communities in the USA (pg 141-287), 1974 October 29 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Panel Transcripts - Additional copies - Panel I, Panel II, Panel III, Panel IV, Panel V (Box 57, Folder 553-568)
  - Background Materials, 1.2
    - General Commission Meeting: Press Conference, 1975 February 28 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - General Commission Meeting: Selected Trends, A Discussion Framework, Prepared by the Center for Integrated Studies, State University of NY at Binghamton, 1973 December 4-5 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - General Commission Meeting Agenda, Correspondence, Memorandum and Notes, 1974 April 1-2 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Panel I, Background Material for Discussion Purposes, 1974 April 1-2 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Panel I, Drafts, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Panel I, Energy Plan Draft, by Edward Fried, and "What Price Oil?" by Walter J. Levy, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Panel I, Hans Mark Notes and Drafts of Meeting, 1974 April 23 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Panel I, Hans Mark Notes on Meeting, 1974 September 11 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Panel I, Menu for Meeting, 1974 September 9 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Panel I, Notes and Correspondence on Meeting, 1974 June 24 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Panel I, Outline of Material in Support of Charge A: Present Situation, Trends and Their Implications, Working Draft (Section 1-4), 1974 June 24 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Panel I, Outline of Material in Support of Charge A: Present Situation, Trends and Their Implications, Working Draft (Section 5-9), 1974 June 24 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Panel I, Pocantico Meting, 1973 April 23 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Panel I, Quality of Life and OECD Article on Oil Prices, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Panel I, Study Staff Book: Agendas, Papers, Presentations and Reports (Section A-J), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Panel I, Study Staff Book: Agendas, Papers, Presentations and Reports (Section K-XYZ), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Panel II, Background Material, Drafts, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Panel II, Background Material for Discussion Purposes, 1974 April 1 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Panel II, Comments on Panel Background Material, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Panel II, Food, Health, World Population and Quality of Life, Part A and B, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - Panel II, Food, Health, World Population and Quality of Life, Background Papers, Volume I, 1975 March (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - Panel II, Food, Health, World Population and Quality of Life, Background Papers, Volume II, 1975 May (Box 11, Folder 83)
    - Panel II, Food, Health, World Population and Quality of Life, Background Papers, Volume II, 1975 May (Box 11, Folder 84)
    - Panel II, Food Trend Statistics, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 85)
    - Panel II, Material Presented at Meeting, 1974 April 1-2 (Box 11, Folder 86)
    - Panel II, NAR Notes, Meeting, 1974 July 22 (Box 11, Folder 87)
    - Panel II, Study Staff Book: Agendas, Papers, Presentations and Reports (Section A-J), 1974 (Box 11, Folder 88)
    - Panel II, Study Staff Book: Agendas, Papers, Presentations and Reports (Section J-YZ), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 89)
    - Panel III, Background Materials for Meeting on Raw Materials, Industrial Development, Capital Formation and World Trade, 1974 May 13 (Box 12, Folder 90)
    - Panel III, Background Materials for Meeting on Raw Materials, Industrial Development, Capital Formation, Employment, and World Trade, 1974 September 30 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Panel Ill, Comments on Panel Background Materials, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Panel III, Materials in Support of Charge A, Present Situation, Trends and Their Implications, Working Draft, 1974 July 29 (Box 12, Folder 93)
    - Panel III, Material in Support of Charge D, Critical Choices Relating to Policy Decisions, Working Draft, 1974 September 12 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - Panel III, Outline and Report of Meeting, 1974 July 29 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - Panel III, Study Staff Book: Agendas, Papers, Presentations and Reports (Section A-M), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - Panel III, Study Staff Book: Agendas, Papers, Presentations and Reports (Section N), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - Panel III, Study Staff Book: Agendas, Papers, Presentations and Reports (Section O-Z), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Panel III, Summary Notes for Meeting on Raw Materials, Industrial Development, Capital Formation and World Trade, 1974 May 13 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Panel IV, Background Material and Report of Meeting on Open Societies and Governments in a World of Centrally Managed Economies, 1974 June 17 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Panel IV, Background Papers Volume I, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Panel IV, Background Papers Volume I, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Panel IV, Background Papers Volume II, 1975 April (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Panel IV, Background Papers Volume II, 1975 April (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Panel IV, Background Papers Volume II, 1974 November (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - Panel IV, Factual and Analytical Background Material, Working Draft, 1974 June 26 (Box 14, Folder 106)
    - Panel IV, International Trade and Monetary Systems, Inflation and the Relationships Among Differing Economic Systems, Part A, Draft (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - Panel IV, NAR Notes, Meeting, 1974 July 19 (Box 14, Folder 108)
    - Panel IV, Open Societies and Centrally Controlled Economies, 1974 June (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - Panel IV, Overseas Private Investment Corporation, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - Panel IV, Overseas Private Investment Corporation, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - Panel IV, Study Staff Book: Agendas, Papers, Presentations and Reports, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - Panel V, Hans Mark Notes, 1974 August 5 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - Panel V, Hellmann Study, "Asia and the Major Powers", Summary, Robert A. Scalapino, undated (Box 14, Folder 114)
    - Panel V, Hellmann Study, japan and America: Old Myths, New Realities, Donald C. Hellmann, undated (Box 14, Folder 115)
    - Panel V, Hellmann Study, "Political and Strategic Aspects of Chinese Foreign Policy", Thomas W. Robinson, undated (Box 15, Folder 116)
    - Panel V, Report and Nates on Meeting on Essential Elements of World Progress, Stability and Peace, 1974 May 28 (Box 15, Folder 117)
    - Panel V, Study Staff Book: Agendas, Papers, Presentations and Reports, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 118)
    - Panel V, Western Europe Study by Landes, and USSR and Eastern Europe Study by Griffith, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    - Panel V, Middle East Study by Udovitch, Asia Study by Hellmann, Latin America Study by Theberge, and Africa Study by Kitchen, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 120)
    - Panel VI, Americas and the Arts: Highlights from a Survey of Public Opinion, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 121)
    - Panel VI, Background Papers and Notes, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    - Panel VI, Background Papers Volume III, Paul H. Weaver and Robert M. Ball, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - Panel VI, Background Papers Volume III, Robert L. Kahn and Angus Campbell, and Gilbert S. Omenn, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - Panel VI, B & C, Hooker and Stark, Draft, 1974 July (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - Panel VI, Charts, Figures, and Tables, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - Panel VI, Charts, Figures, and Tables, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 127)
    - Panel VI, Drafts and Status Report, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 128)
    - Panel VI, Drafts for Meeting on Quality of Life of Individuals and Communities in the USA, 1974 October (Box 16, Folder 129)
    - Panel VI, Draft Outline of Final Report, Elspeth Rostow, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 130)
    - Panel VI, Elspeth Rostow Papers, Draft, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 131)
    - Panel VI, Elspeth Rostow Papers, Draft, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 132)
    - Panel VI, Forty Under Forty, 1974 May 17 (Box 16, Folder 133)
    - Panel VI, Hooker, Preamble, Draft, 1974-1975 December 12 (Box 16, Folder 134)
    - Panel VI, Mitre Corporation Reports, 1971, 1973, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - Panel VI, Mitre Corporation Report, Correspondence and Memorandum, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 136)
    - Panel VI, Mitre Corporation Report, Transportation in the US: An Appraisal, 1975 January (Box 17, Folder 137)
    - Panel VI, Mitre Corporation, An Appraisal of the US Transportation System, Draft, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 138)
    - Panel VI, Mitre Corporation, An Appraisal of the US Transportation System, Draft, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 139)
    - Panel VI, Notes and Correspondence, Quality of Life of Individuals and Communities, 1974 June 3 (Box 17, Folder 140)
    - Panel VI, NYS Study of Significant National Trends and Policies of Concern to NYS: Division of the Budget, 1974 July 15 (Box 17, Folder 141)
    - Panel VI, NYS Study of Significant National Trends and Policies of Concern to NYS: Division of the Budget, 1974 July 15 (Box 17, Folder 142)
    - Panel VI, Social Indicators and Quality of Life, 1970, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 143)
    - Panel VI, Study Staff Book: Agendas, Papers, Presentations and Reports, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 144)
    - Approach of the Study by the CCCA, Working Outlines, 1974 March 11 (Box 18, Folder 145)
    - Background Materials on Population, National Economy, Public Sector, and Private Sector, undated (Box 18, Folder 146)
    - Background Materials on Social Indicators, and National Goals and Objectives, undated (Box 18, Folder 147)
    - A Bibliographical Survey of Futurology, undated (Box 18, Folder 148)
    - Charge to Commission, Drafts, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 149)
    - Critical Choices as the US Enters its Third Century, Willis W. Harman, Stanford Research Institute, 1973 October (Box 18, Folder 150)
    - The Domestic Council, 1974 December 9 (Box 18, Folder 151)
    - D.C. Health Contract Drafts and Preliminary Materials, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 152)
    - Items for Steering Committee Meeting, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 153)
    - Members of the CCCA Pamphlet, undated (Box 18, Folder 154)
    - Newspaper Articles, Panel I, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 155)
    - Newspaper Articles, Panel II, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 156)
    - Newspaper Articles, Panel III, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 157)
    - Newspaper Articles, Panel IV, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 158)
    - Newspaper Articles, Panel V, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 159)
    - Newspaper Articles, Panel VI, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 160)
    - The Next 200 Years: A Scenario for America and the World, Herman Kahn, William Brown and Leon Martel, Work in Progress (Chapter 1-4), 1975 (Box 19, Folder 161)
    - The Next 200 Years: A Scenario for America and the World, Herman Kahn, William Brown and Leon Martel, Work in Progress (Chapter 5-9), 1975 (Box 19, Folder 162)
    - The Present Military Balance and Trends, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 163)
    - Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 164)
    - Reports and Magazines on Coal Mining, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 165)
    - Schedule of Panel Meetings, 1974 March-April (Box 19, Folder 166)
    - Statement by NAR, 1973 May 14 (Box 19, Folder 167)
    - Study Outlines and Notes, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 168)
    - Technology Development and the National Purpose, Hans Mark, 1974 November 1 (Box 19, Folder 169)
    - Technology Development and the National Purpose, Hans Mark, with letter to NAR, 1974 November 1 (Box 19, Folder 170)
    - United States Issues Between Now and the Year 2000, Herman Kahn, Hudson Institute Memo, 1973 October (Box 19, Folder 171)
    - World and National situation, Jay W. Forrester, 1973 November 12 (Box 20, Folder 172)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings and Notes, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 173)
    - Miscellaneous Panel Materials, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 174)
    - Miscellaneous Panel Materials, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 175)
    - Miscellaneous Panel Materials, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 176)
    - Miscellaneous Panel Materials, undated (Box 20, Folder 177)
  - Laurance S. Rockefeller's CCCA materials, 1.3
    - Panel I, Appendices to Energy and its Relationship to Economics, Ecology and World Stability, Preliminary Drafts (Appendices 1-2, 4, 6, 17), 1974 December (Box 20, Folder 178)
    - Panel I, Appendices to Energy and its Relationship to Economics, Ecology and World Stability, Preliminary Drafts (Appendices 3, 5, 8, 10-16, 18-20, 22), 1974 December (Box 20, Folder 179)
    - Panel I, Background Material for Discussion Purposes, 1974 April 1-2 (Box 21, Folder 180)
    - Panel I, Background Materials on Energy, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 181)
    - Panel I, Background Materials on Energy, Edward Teller, undated (Box 21, Folder 182)
    - Panel I, Background Material for Meeting, 1974 April 1-2 (Box 21, Folder 183)
    - Panel I, Energy and Its Relationship to Ecology Economics and World Stability, Report Draft, 1975 June 13 (Box 21, Folder 184)
    - Panel I, Presentations Made at Meeting of Commission, 1974 April 2 (Box 21, Folder 185)
    - Panel II, Food, Health, World Population and Quality of Life, Report Draft, 1975 June 16 (Box 21, Folder 186)
    - Panel IV, Background Papers, International Trade and Monetary Systems, Inflation and the Relationships among Differing Economic Systems, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 187)
    - Panel IV, Background Papers, International Trade and Monetary Systems, Inflation and the Relationships among Differing Economic Systems, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 188)
    - Panel V, Transcript of CCCA Meeting, 1975 February 28 (Box 22, Folder 189)
    - Panel V, Press Conference, 1975 February 28 (Box 22, Folder 190)
    - Panel VI, Background Papers, Volume 1, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 191)
    - Panel VI, Background Papers, Volume 1, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 192)
    - Panel VI, Background Papers, Volume 2, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 193)
    - Panel VI, Background Papers, Volume 2, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 194)
    - Panel VI, Background Papers, Volume 3, Kahn and Omenn, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 195)
    - Panel VI, Background Papers, Volume 3, Weaver and Ball, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 196)
    - Panel VI, Background Papers, Volume 4, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 197)
    - Panel VI, Forty Under Forty, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 198)
    - Panel VI, Papers from Laurance Rockefeller's Forty Under Forty Binder, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 199)